Meet the man behind the hero.
Sly is a documentary film directed by Thom Zimny.
His love of film began as an escape from a rocky childhood.
From underdog to Hollywood legend, Sylvester Stallone
tells his story in this documentary.
Self, played by Sylvester Stallone.
Self, played by Arnold Schwarzenegger.
Self, played by Frank Stallone Jr..
Self, played by Quentin Tarantino.
Self, played by Talia Shire.
Self, played by Henry Winkler.
Sly is a 2023 American documentary film about the life and legacy
of Sylvester Stallone, directed by Thom Zimny.
It premiered at the 2023 Toronto International Film Festival,
and was released on Netflix on November 3, 2023.
The film explores themes of show business,
biography, movie star, candid, celebrities.